{
  "anatomy": [
    {
      "question": "What does the eyelids do?",
      "options": [
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye...",
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape...",
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ...",
        "There are 6 extraocular muscles controlling eye movement: the superior rectus moves the eye up, the ..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the fibrous tunic do?",
      "options": [
        "There are 6 extraocular muscles controlling eye movement: the superior rectus moves the eye up, the ...",
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape...",
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye...",
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the sclera do?",
      "options": [
        "There are 6 extraocular muscles controlling eye movement: the superior rectus moves the eye up, the ...",
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape...",
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye...",
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the extraocular muscles do?",
      "options": [
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ...",
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye...",
        "There are 6 extraocular muscles controlling eye movement: the superior rectus moves the eye up, the ...",
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the cornea do?",
      "options": [
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape...",
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye...",
        "The cornea is the clear, front part of the eye that helps focus light and shields it from dirt and d...",
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the tear film do?",
      "options": [
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape...",
        "The tear film, often called the pre-corneal layers, have three layers that keep your eyes healthy an...",
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ...",
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the corneal layers do?",
      "options": [
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ...",
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape...",
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye...",
        "The cornea has five layers that work together to protect the eye and maintain vision. The epithelium..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the vascular tunic do?",
      "options": [
        "The vascular tunic, or uvea, is the middle layer of the eye responsible for providing blood supply, ...",
        "The eyelids protect your eyes, keep them moist, and control how much light gets in. They’re your eye...",
        "The fibrous tunic, the eye's outer layer, includes the sclera and cornea. The sclera maintains shape...",
        "The sclera is the white, tough outer layer of the eye that protects its inner structures, maintains ..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ],
  "pathology": [
    {
      "question": "What does the arcus senilis do?",
      "options": [
        "General placeholder content",
        "General placeholder content",
        "A cataract is a clouding of the lens of the eye, leading to a decrease in vision.",
        "Arcus senilis is a gray or white arc visible above and below the outer part of the cornea."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the cataract do?",
      "options": [
        "A cataract is a clouding of the lens of the eye, leading to a decrease in vision.",
        "General placeholder content",
        "Arcus senilis is a gray or white arc visible above and below the outer part of the cornea.",
        "General placeholder content"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ],
  "physiology": [
    {
      "question": "What does the cell structure do?",
      "options": [
        "General placeholder content",
        "General placeholder content",
        "Ocular physiology examines how the eye structures work together to create vision.",
        "Physiology studies the structure and function of cells, including their energy production, reproduct..."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the physiology do?",
      "options": [
        "General placeholder content",
        "General placeholder content",
        "Physiology studies the structure and function of cells, including their energy production, reproduct...",
        "Ocular physiology examines how the eye structures work together to create vision."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    }
  ],
  "test": [
    {
      "question": "What does the card 1 do?",
      "options": [
        "Elit saepe id aspernatur quae veniam iure? Quidem iure sit praesentium eaque tempore. Nihil quis mol...",
        "Elit saepe id aspernatur quae veniam iure? Quidem iure sit praesentium eaque tempore. Nihil quis mol...",
        "General placeholder content",
        "General placeholder content"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the card 2 do?",
      "options": [
        "General placeholder content",
        "Elit saepe id aspernatur quae veniam iure? Quidem iure sit praesentium eaque tempore. Nihil quis mol...",
        "Elit saepe id aspernatur quae veniam iure? Quidem iure sit praesentium eaque tempore. Nihil quis mol...",
        "General placeholder content"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    }
  ]
}